A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential records, Video Recordings, Series 20 FA798
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Video Recordings, 1974-1978; 20; 5.4 Cubic Feet; 64 video recordings.
  - Senate Rules Committee: Nelson A. Rockefeller's Vice Presidential Hearings - Reconvening - Day Four (Tape 15), 1974 November 13; U-matic; Sound, Color, 62 minutes (Box 6, Tape AV 12021)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Intermittent audio distortion and buzz throughout beginning of Nelson Rockefeller's statement.
  - Senate Rules Committee: Nelson A. Rockefeller's Vice Presidential Hearings - Reconvening - Day Four (Tape 16), 1974 November 13; U-matic; Sound, Color, 62 minutes (Box 7, Tape AV 12022)
    Tape begins with continuation of Nelson Rockefeller's opening statement.
    He finishes speaking about his financial matters, and makes closing remarks about wealth and power.
    Senator Howard Cannon begins cross-examination, particularly about the Arthur Goldberg book.
    Senator Hugh Scott asks questions about Rockefeller's taxes.
    Senator Clairborne Pells asks why no deduction was taken on the losses from the Goldberg book. He asks about Rockefeller's views about proper use of and amount of money given to a candidate.
  - Senate Rules Committee: Nelson A. Rockefeller's Vice Presidential Hearings - Reconvening - Day Four (Tape 17), 1974 November 13; U-matic; Sound, Color, 62 minutes (Box 7, Tape AV 12023)
    Continuation of Day 4.
    Senator Robert Griffin begins questioning about the Goldberg book. Rockefeller speaks about his finances, net worth, real estate, and artworks.
    First day session takes a recess and resumes after lunch
    Senator Robert Byrd extensively questions Rockefeller about the Arthur Goldberg book.
  - Senate Rules Committee: Nelson A. Rockefeller's Vice Presidential Hearings - Reconvening - Day Four (Tape 18), 1974 November 13; Sound, Color, 62 minutes; U-matic (Box 7, Tape AV 12024)
    Continuation of Day 4
    Nelson Rockefeller and Senator Byrd finish their terse exchange about how the information regarding the Goldberg book became public.
    Senator Mark Hatfield begins questioning Rockefeller about the millions of dollars in gifts to friends and associates, including Henry Kissinger. Question about Nelson Rockefeller's association between CIA and Rockefeller family interests in Latin America.
    Hatfield discusses relationship between India and USA, and Ford Foundation and Rockefeller Foundation role in India famine relief in 1960s. Rockefeller discusses the Green Revolution and need for countries to be self sustaining. World hunger, aid, and national security are discussed in depth.
    Senator James Allen asks Rockefeller's opinion on a reduction of federal expenditures. Allen asks about Rockefeller's personal loans to Dr. William J. Ronan.
    Allen asks about political campaign contributions and Rockefeller family members contributing to Nelson Rockefeller campaigns over the years.
    Senator Harrison Williams asks about Arthur Goldberg book and Rockefeller's gifts to Dr. Ronan.
  - Senate Rules Committee: Nelson A. Rockefeller's Vice Presidential Hearings - Reconvening - Day Four (Tape 19), 1974 November 13; U-matic; Sound, Color, 62 minutes (Box 7, Tape AV 12025)
    Tape begins with Senator Hugh Scott discussing the Arthur Goldberg book.
    Senator Howard Cannon makes statements about the Goldberg book and whether Rockefeller misled the FBI investigation into the book. Rockefeller speaks about contributions to the Academy of Political Science and their "Governing New York State: The Rockefeller Years." Cannon presents new analysis of Rockefeller's net worth and finances.
    Senator Claiborne Pell asks Rockefeller whether he know how Stuart Scott became ambassador to Portugal. Pell requests details regarding Rockefeller's pardon of Judd Morehouse.
    Senator James Allen asks Rockefeller about recruiting employees and his providing financial assistance. Allen questions Rockefeller's loan to Dr. William J. Ronan.
    Senator Harrison Williams questions gifts to public employees, including Dr. Ronan. Rockefeller provides MTA history.
    Senator Hugh Scott reads sworn testimony about Judd Morehouse.
  - Senate Rules Committee: Nelson A. Rockefeller's Vice Presidential Hearings - Reconvening - Day Four (Tape 20), 1974 November 13; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 7, Tape AV 12026)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 21, 1974 November 14; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 7, Tape AV 12027)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 22, 1974 November 14; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 7, Tape AV 12028)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 23, 1974 November 14; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 8, Tape AV 12029)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 24, 1974 November 14; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 8, Tape AV 12030)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 25, 1974 November 14; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 8, Tape AV 12031)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 26, 1974 November 14; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 8, Tape AV 12032)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 27, 1974 November 15; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 8, Tape AV 12033)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 28, 1974 November 15; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 8, Tape AV 12034)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 29, 1974 November 15; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 8, Tape AV 12035)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 30, 1974 November 15; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 9, Tape AV 12036)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 31, 1974 November 15; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 9, Tape AV 12037)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 32, 1974 November 15; 1974 November 18; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 9, Tape AV 12038)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 33, 1974 November 18; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 9, Tape AV 12039)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 34, 1974 November 18; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 9, Tape AV 12040)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 35, 1974 November 18; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 9, Tape AV 12041)
  - Nelson A Rockefeller Confirmation Tape 36, 1974 November 18; Sound, Color; U-matic (Box 9, Tape AV 12042)
  - Star Magazine Television Commercial Featuring Happy Rockefeller, circa 1974; U-matic; Sound, Color (Box 10, Tape AV 12043)
    Tape begins with a TV commercial for tabloid "Star" magazine that has a story about "Unhappy" Rockefeller and shows footage of Happy Rockefeller. Remainder of tape contains a TV program "Petrocelli".
    General